export const Data = [
    {
        question: "Why did the bike fall over?",
        answer: "It was two tired."
    },
    {
        question: "What did the policeman say to his belly button?",
        answer: "You’re under a vest."
    },
    {
        question: "Why did the man get hit by a bike every day?",
        answer: "He was stuck in a vicious cycle."
    },
    {
        question: "What’s the difference between the bird flu and the swine flu?",
        answer: "One requires tweetment and the other an oinkment."
    },
    {
        question: "Why do people say “break a leg” when you go on stage?",
        answer: "Because every play has a cast."
    },
    {
        question: "Why are there gates around cemeteries?",
        answer: "Because people are dying to get in."
    },
    {
        question: "Why shouldn’t you write with a broken pen?",
        answer: "Because it’s pointless."
    },
    {
        question: "Why did the bike fall over?",
        answer: "It was two tired."
    },
    {
        question: "What did the yoga instructor say when her landlord tried to evict her?",
        answer: "Namaste."
    },
    {
        question: "What do you call fake spaghetti?",
        answer: "An im-pasta."
    },


]